Man, I'm starving.
After we visit Bro's grave,
let's get something to eat, Josuke.
Eh, I'm not hungry.
ITALIAN CUISINE
TRENDY
100 METERS TO THE LEFT
There's a new Italian restaurant.
Looks like it's just up the road.
ITALIAN CUISINE
Just up the road is the cemetery.
Doesn't seem like
the best location for a new restaurant.
Josuke, it's foodie destinations
like that that bring people in!
"This is to die for!
My mouth can't stop watering!"
I'm sure that's what people say!
Let's go! Come on!
This is it?
TRENDY
I thought this was
a vacant building…
Maybe they remodeled.
It's got character!
What? "Diner dependent"?
TODAY'S MENU
DINER DEPENDENT
WITH COFFEE & DESSERT
3,500 YEN—
Great atmosphere inside, too!
Welcome.
EPISODE 10
LET'S GO EAT SOME ITALIAN FOOD
Two today?
Please, have a seat.
Uh… Thanks…
Please.
R-Right…
Um, are you a foreigner?
Si, Signore. I'm from Italy.
I'm Tonio Trendy.
Call me Tonio.
Yay, this is great!
I get to eat real Italian food!
I traveled to many countries,
and incorporated the best of
the world's culinary traditions
with the flavors of my homeland.
Then I came to Japan
looking for new opportunities.
Morioh is a wonderful town.
You can find many farms
with many kinds of fresh produce.
Its "treasures of the sea"
are wonderful, too.
I like it here very much.
Using Morioh's wonderful ingredients,
I will make you gentlemen
a meal to delight your senses.
All right!
Now what should I get?
Show us the menu immediately!
Menu?
We have no such thing here.
What do you mean
you don't have a menu?
What I serve depends on
who is dining.
So show me the menu!
No, no! I examine my customer,
and then decide what to prepare.
What're you talking about?
So you don't let your customers
eat what they want?
Yesterday, you suffered
a bout of diarrhea, no?
Your intestinal walls are inflamed.
And you're sleep deprived.
You got in only four hours,
am I right?
That explains your puffy eyes.
Now let's see your left hand.
Uh-huh…
Your right foot is infected
with athlete's foot.
You also have two cavities,
and your left shoulder is stiff, right?
H-How do you know all that?!
Everything you said was spot on!
Your hands tell me everything
about your physical condition.
Oh, please excuse me!
And you, Signore?
Yeah, I'm not very hungry.
Just coffee'll be fine.
Make it a cappuccino.
Ho capito.
You do know, super healthy food
usually tastes like crap.
If it tastes even a little gross,
we don't have to pay.
We can complain and leave.
Right.
J-Josuke…
This water…
Or this mineral water…
What's wrong?
I-I've never in my
entire life had water this good!
It's like… it's brimming with elegance.
It's like something a princess in the Alps
playing a harp would drink.
It's gloriously fresh and smooth!
Like that first taste of water after
wandering in the desert for three days!
Y-You aren't kidding!
It's amazing!
Superb!
You're right, it is superb.
What brand of water is this?
I-It's so amazing
I think I'm gonna cry.
Come on, a little sip
of water isn't worth weeping over.
It must be its purity.
Do you have a handkerchief?
The tears are gushing.
They just keep coming!
They won't stop!
O-Okuyasu!
Hey, you're acting weird.
Are you okay?
O-Okuyasu!
Wh-What is with these tears?!
They keep pouring out of me!
Okuyasu, y-your eyes, the eyeball,
the white part…
It's all shriveled and loose!
Momento! Please be calm.
Y-You bastard!
What did you give Okuyasu to drink?
Please calm yourselves.
His eyes are only temporarily withered.
That mineral water is
50,000-year old melted snow
from Mount Kilimanjaro in Africa.
It flushes the eye's interior
of contaminants,
and is an effective
treatment for sleep deprivation.
The reason you didn't cry
from drinking the water is
because you obtained
adequate sleep last night.
Josuke!
My sleepiness is completely gone!
I feel flawless!
Like I slept a full ten hours!
Are you serious?
O-Okuyasu, you sure there's
nothing wrong with your eyes?
Josuke, when you drink water
this good for the first time,
the tears will flow.
I cried more when I watched
Champ on video.
Is that so?
Yes!
Your cappuccino.
R-Right…
Shall we continue
with the next course?
Ooh, this looks good!
INGREDIENTS
• MOZZARELLA CHEESE
(4 PIECES, THINLY SLICED)
• TOMATO (5 PIECES, THINLY SLICED)
For our antipasto,
we have insalata Caprese.
TONIO'S SPECIAL HOUSE DRESSING
• 1 ANCHOVY FILLET • WAKAME
• OLIVE OIL • WHITE WINE VINEGAR
• LEMON JUICE • SALT • PEPPER
• BASIL (ON TOP) • TOASTED BREAD
• LETTUCE (FOR GARNISH)
(SERVE IMMEDIATELY)
M-M-Mozzaza?
Mozzarella is a soft, fresh,
low-fat cheese.
It's a national favorite in Italy.
The first people to use tomatoes as
a culinary ingredient were the Italians.
The Italian people are the world's
leaders of tomato-based cuisine.
That is not bravado.
That is pride.
Please, enjoy.
If you say so!
Well, I guess it is pretty good.
It's good. Very good.
But… I'm not sure what it is,
this cheese doesn't taste like much.
No! No!
You eat it together with the tomato.
What? With the tomato?
Well, most foreign food is incompatible
with Japanese tastes.
My god!
Huh?!
The tomatoey nectar caresses
the fresh, delicate cheese!
The cheese accentuates the tomato,
and the tomato enriches the cheese!
It's a symphony, a harmony of flavors!
It's like Simon and Garfunkel!
Or Ucchan and Nanchan!
It's like the writer-illustrator duo
Asao Takamori and Tetsuya Chiba
from Ashita no Joe!
Grazie!
Nothing makes me happier
than knowing you enjoyed it.
H-Hey, Okuyasu.
Let me have some.
No way.
Order your own!
You're not getting any of this!
I wouldn't give you a piece even
if you were starving to death.
Yuuumy!
Thank you for
giving birth to me, Mom!
Shit! I knew you were
a cheap bastard, but this!
Fine. I'll have one too.
Ho capito.
But the only one getting
his stiff shoulder corrected
is the man with the stiff
shoulder, sitting right there.
Huh? Stiff shoulder?
You know,
my neck does feel kinda hot.
Weird, it's all sweaty.
Signore, may I suggest
you remove your jacket.
I'm getting…
I-I-I'm all itchy!
There's all this flakey stuff
sticking to my fingers!
That is dead skin.
Dead skin?!
It's proof your metabolic
function and circulation has improved.
The calcium, vitamins,
and minerals of the antipasto
have stimulated your thyroid
and its metabolic hormone secretion.
The harmful cells are
being expelled as dead skin.
Please keep scratching,
and remove all that dead skin!
Okuyasu, stop scratching!
You've scratched off
a softball's worth of skin!
You're digging into
your shoulder's muscle!
N-No! You're wrong, Josuke!
So supple!
My shoulder is crazy flexible now!
It's so flexible and light,
it's like it's floating!
Look! Look what my shoulders
can do now!
I've never been able to do this!
That stiffness is good and gone!
Now, if you will excuse me
for a moment.
I have to keep an eye on the pasta.
Amazing!
That Chef Tonio is a genius!
N-No…
This is getting freaky!
There's nothing normal
about this guy's cooking!
MORIOH LANDMARK 3
"ITALIAN RESTAURANT TRENDY"
HOW TO GET THERE: 1 MINUTE'S WALK
FROM MAIN STOP OFF POINT OF MORIOH
KUNIMI MOUNTAIN PASS CEMETARY BUS
AN ECCENTRIC RESTAURANT WHERE
THERE IS NO SET MENU,
AND WHERE THE CHEF DECIDES
HIS MENU ON THE BASIS OF
EACH CUSTOMER'S PHYSICAL CONDITION.
SEATING IS LIMITED.
RESERVATIONS ARE RECOMMENDED.
Now, shall we continue
with our meal?
Now for our Primo piatto.
Today is pasta.
Spaghetti alla puttanesca!
INGREDIENTS
• SPAGHETTI • PITTED BLACK OLIVES
• OLIVE OIL • ANCHOVY FILLET
• GARLIC • CHILI FLAKES
• CHERRY TOMATOES
• PARSLEY, SALT, PEPPER
• PARMESAN CHEESE
(SERVE PIPING HOT)
Literally "whore's pasta,"
the name is said to have
originated with prostitutes
who favored the dish's
easy preparation and
uniquely delectable flavors.
Cheese is not usually added to
pasta prepared with garlic,
but this dish is an exception.
Does this spaghetti
have chili flakes in it?
Yes, it does.
ROME
NAPLES
SPAGHETTI TAGLIATELLE LINGUINE
FUSILLI PENNE FARFALLE
LASAGNE CONCHIGLIE TUBETTI
The sauce in Spaghetti Puttanesca is
one of the oldest recipes
of Italian cuisine.
And my hometown, Naples,
is considered its birthplace.
I give it my highest recommendation.
Oh, but… I can't eat spicy things.
The only kind of curry rice
I can handle is
that mild Vermont Curry
that has apples and honey in it.
Wasabi with sushi is no good, either.
I can't! It's too spicy!
This is way too spicy!
If you can't eat spicy food, Okuyasu,
then don't eat it.
If it doesn't please you,
please don't force yourself.
I'm happy to take
the pasta off your bill.
I will now prepare your
main course, the secondo piatto.
But you know sir,
I make my spaghetti to be enjoyed
even by those who cannot
tolerate spicy food.
Being sensitive to spiciness is okay?
Hot!
Look, I know he's a master chef,
that Tonio…
There's no question, he's a genius!
But this wasn't his best work.
No, I think you may've lucked out
with your spice intolerance.
Don't you think this food and
that water are a little too weird?
Something's shady!
Shady? Like what?
Spicy!
You produced a softball-sized wad
of dead skin,
and cried a river back there!
I guess I did…
When I went to Shirabu Onsen
in Yamagata,
I lost even more dead skin,
and my back got better!
That's totally normal.
Hot!
Listen! Remember what
Toshikazu Hazamada said.
For whatever reason,
whether or not they know each other…
Stand users are
inadvertently drawn to each other.
Josuke!
Are you saying Tonio is
a Stand user?
Shh! We don't know for sure yet!
That's why I said "shady"!
Shady, eh?
Hot! No way!
If you don't like spicy food,
quit putting it in your mouth!
You're right.
Spicy food and me don't mix, but…
for some reason,
I can't stop tasting this sauce.
Why are you eating that?!
I-I know!
Usually I can't eat stuff this spicy…
But…
I can't stop. After that first bite,
the spiciness just pulled me in.
It's like eating your age
in beans during Setsubun,
and even though they don't taste good,
before you know it,
you've eaten a whole bag!
Hey, I told you to stop eating!
I'm getting hungrier!
The more I eat,
the more I want to scarf down!
It's so good!
Okuyasu, you…
Your tooth!
You just lost your tooth!
My cavity!
My rotten tooth fell out!
Actually, I think I had
a cavity below, too…
Another rotten tooth!
Your tooth!
A molar is already growing in?!
That's it.
I don't know what he's scheming…
Shining Diamond!
I wanted to eat more…
I'm gonna revert the ingredients
to their original forms!
What were those little things?
A Stand!
So Tonio Trendy is a Stand user,
after all!
Are you okay, Okuyasu?
My sleepiness is gone.
My stiffness melted away,
and my cavities were replaced
with healthy teeth, but…
M-My stomach hurts!
It's excruciating!
Wait!
Tonio! What the hell
are you pulling here?!
Where is he?
So he finished our main course…
Good, good… You enjoy that.
It appears my main dish of lamb
with apple relish was a success.
What?!
And what are you doing there?
So you saw!
So you came in here to spy on me?!
You will pay for this! Get ready!
Why should I have to stand here listening
to you threatening me to pay?
That's my line!
Just what the hell are you trying
to do with that "food" of yours?!
Okuyasu!
What are you eating?!
I can't stand it! My stomach hurts,
but I can't stop eating!
The tangy-sweet apple relish
and juice from the lamb
makes every bite pure ecstasy!
To think food could taste like this!
Drop that meat, Okuyasu!
The joy!
The pleasure keeps on going!
Amazing!
M-My guts…
My stomach!
Okuyasu!
You'll pay for this!
You bastard!
Wash your hands with soap right now!
MEDICATED
Huh?!
It's inexcusable!
Entering a kitchen
without permission is inexcusable!
You!
Cleanliness in the kitchen
is number one!
S-Soap?
You want me to wash my hands?
Hey, Josuke!
My insides feel rejuvenated!
I feel full, too.
I feel totally content.
Huh?!
My poopy tummy's all better!
What?!
Well isn't that magnificent!
Knowing my cooking brought
happiness and health to my customer
gives me no greater joy or happiness.
That puppy…
With such unconventional flavors,
I wanted him to taste it first.
His digestion was off, too.
Y-You… really only wanted
Okuyasu to enjoy a good meal?
What else could a chef want?
It is what I live for.
It is all I hope for.
So you're a Stand user.
We are, too.
Oh, I don't believe it!
When… When I was traveling
the world
searching for the perfect cuisine,
I discovered my powers.
Never before have I met
anyone with similar powers.
But…
You need some common sense!
Huh?
You touched my kitchen without
washing your hands!
A kitchen's worst enemy is germs!
That's why I was angry!
H-Huh? I-I'm sorry!
I wasn't thinking!
You had better be ready!
Now, shall we continue
with the cooking?
Dessert is… pudding?
But I'm a tough guy!
Hmph! What a load of crap.
My god!
You really are a genius!
A chef of your caliber
makes me proud
- to be a resident of Morioh!
- Dammit, Okuyasu!
Should I assume you enjoyed that?
Hey! I don't see any scrubbing!
Miserable…
Hey, my athlete's foot is gone!
I shall await your return. Grazie!
TRENDY
POLE JAM
Jotaro Kujo, I presume?
I'm with the Speedwagon Foundation.
For now, any electrical wiring
poses a threat,
that includes phone lines
and power lines.
That is why I've come
to deliver this message in the flesh.
"I expect to arrive at
the port of Morioh at noon, tomorrow.
—Joseph Joestar."
EPISODE 11
CHILI PEPPER, PART 1